(+84)964196652pvbang23092002@gmail.com

PHAN VAN BANG

Mobile Developer

github.com/ilyouu linkedin.com/in/pv-bang

SUMMARY

I'm a 3rd-year university student majoring in information technology with experience in Mobile Development and Web Development. During my studies, I did some projects which are highly appreciated. I also spend time learning new technologies and best practices to become a better engineer.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: Java, Javascript & Typescript, HTML/CSS

 Frameworks / Platforms: ReactNative, Laravel, ReactJS, Web API, Docker

 Databases: MySQL, MS SQL Server Vietnamese, English Languagues:

EXPERIENCES

Mobile Developer

Chat Application Mar. 2022 - Jun. 2022

 Built a chat application. Have features such as chat, group chat, video call, audio call, add friends, manager profile, post the story, voice search,...

- In this project I build the whole project from scratch using:

 - Firebase for data persistent
 - Jitsi Meet for call video, call audio
- Github Repo: https://github.com/ilyouu/java-meeting-client-server

Mobile Developer (React Native)

Solve Math Exercises Aug. 2022 - Sep. 2022

- Built a mobile app to solve math exercises for students from grade 1 to grade 12
- In this project I build the whole project from scratch using:
 - React Native for Frontend
 - Laravel website below to make Backend (API)
- Github Repo: https://github.com/ilyouu/react-native-solve-math-excercises

Web Developer (Laravel)

Solve Math Exercises

- Built a website to solve math exercises for students from grade 1 to grade 12
- In this project I also build the whole project from scratch using:
 - MySQL for data persistent
 - Laravel for Backend, RESTful API
 - MDBootstrap for Frontend
 - Self-developed CDN system basic
- Github Repo: https://github.com/ilyouu/laravel-solve-math-exercises

EDUCATION

Engineering Degree - Information Technology

2020 - Now

Vietnam - Korea University of Information and Communication Technology

Da Nang city, Vietnam

Jul. 2022 - Sep. 2022